worldchampionnetwork.com 2019-07-26

# PRIVACY POLICY | World Champion Network

### **Last revised: April 19, 2019**

World Champion Network believes your privacy is important. This Privacy Policy governs each Service, mobile site, application, and/or other service, regardless of how distributed, transmitted, published, or broadcast (each, a "Service”) provided by WorldChampionNetwork.com (“World Champion Network”), its parent, subsidiaries and/or affiliates (“we,” "us," or “our”) that links to this Privacy Policy, which is binding on all those who access, visit and/or use the Service, whether acting as an individual or on behalf of an entity, including you and all persons, entities, or digital engines of any kind that harvest, crawl, index, scrape, spider, or mine digital content by an automated or manual process or otherwise (collectively, “you” or “your”).

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. You can access this Privacy Policy any time in the footer of the Service's home page or initial screen.  **Your access, visitation and/or use of the Service, including without limitation any registration on any aspect of the Service, will constitute your agreement to this Privacy Policy.**  IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THESE TERMS, YOUR PERMISSION TO VISIT, ACCESS AND/OR USE THE SERVICE IS AUTOMATICALLY AND IMMEDIATELY REVOKED AND YOU MUST EXIT AND DISCONTINUE USE OF THE SERVICE IMMEDIATELY.

**  
1\. Introduction:**  This Privacy Policy describes how World Champion Network treats personal information that World Champion Network collects and receives from you through this Service and other online locations such as Facebook and Twitter.

**  
2\. Agreement to Privacy Policy and Updates:**  World Champion Network may revise the Privacy Policy at any time by posting the revised Privacy Policy on the Service. We display the "Last Revised" date under the title of the Privacy Policy so that you will know when there has been a change. You should check the Privacy Policy on a regular basis for the most current Privacy Policy. Each time you access, use or browse the Service, you signify your acceptance of the then-current Privacy Policy applying to your personal information collected by us on and from the effective date of such changes.

Any changes in the Privacy Policy will take effect upon posting and apply only to information collected from you on and after Last Revised date, unless we provide notice or have other communications with you.

**  
3\. Collection of Personal Information:**  World Champion Network collects personal information about you whenever you access the Service, browse and view Content, request information or materials, participate in Activities, post Submissions or transact business with World Champion Network Entities.

The personal information that World Champion Network collects about you may include without limitation your first and last name, home address, email address, home telephone number, employer name, work address, gender, viewing, preferences, and other information that is not otherwise publicly available. When you choose to log into the Service using your Facebook user profile, for example, World Champion Network may collect your name and email address associated with your Facebook profile. Once you login or subscribe to the Service, you are not anonymous to us. World Champion Network may acquire personal information from vendors that may share the information as permitted in their privacy policies, or from other third parties. World Champion Network may combine personal information with information available from other online or offline sources (such as offline records or publicly available information). If the combined information permits us to contact you online or offline, we will treat the combined information as personal information.

In addition to the information you provide and the other methods described above, World Champion Network collects the domain names and IP addresses of its users, along with usage statistics and browsing history. We may also collect information using cookies, web beacons or similar technologies, or through third parties using similar technologies. These methods permit us to collect various types of information, including which third party Services you visit, pages you visit, how you use the Service, which of our email messages you read, and other information.

Personal information collected by World Champion Network may be stored and processed in the United States in accordance with the laws of the United States. By using the Service, you expressly consent to the storage and processing of your personal information in the United States in accordance with the laws of the United States.

Your Submissions may be available to other Service users and to users of other Services and services. You can choose to avoid including personal information in your Submissions.

**  
4\. Use of Information:**  We may use the information we collect directly and from others:

• To provide you with personalized content and advertising.

• To provide information to third parties that may provide you with personalized content and advertising about their products and services.

• To monitor and analyze information regarding your browsing and viewing preferences.

• To provide analytics for third party advertisers.

• To post Submissions and administer Activities.

• To process and respond to your inquiries.

• To improve the Service.

• To alert you to new features, terms, Content, Activities, or special events, products or services.

• For the purposes for which you provided the information.

**  
5\. Communications with You:**  You authorize World Champion Network to transmit email to you to respond to your communications and administer Activities. In addition, if you have connected your Facebook account to the Service, you agree that World Champion Network is authorized to send you announcements, updates and informational and promotional emails and postal mail from World Champion Network Entities. If you participate in Activities, you agree that World Champion Network is authorized to contact prospective winners by telephone and send information, documents and prizes to you by email or postal mail, as provided in the applicable rules. Unsubscribe instructions are included in each promotional email from World Champion Network. Please note that such requests may take up to ten (10) days to become effective. You may not opt out of receiving communications regarding your dealings with the Service or technical information about the Service.

**  
6\. Information Sharing with Third Parties:**  World Champion Network may disclose the information it collects to others (i) to provide services to you; (ii) to provide information to third parties to enable third parties to provide information to you about their products and services; (iii) to provide analytics to third parties for advertising purposes; (iv) for purposes of outsourcing one or more of the functions described in this Privacy Policy to service providers; (v) to confirm or update information provided by you; (vi) to inform you of important information; (vii) in the event of any reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or disposition of all or any portion of World Champion Network’s business or operations (including without limitation in connection with bankruptcy or any similar proceedings); or (viii) as otherwise authorized by you. We also may share your information in response to a subpoena, legal order or official request, when we believe you have acted in violation of the Terms, to investigate, prevent or take action regarding suspected illegal activities, fraud or potential threats, or exercise legal rights or defend against claims, when we believe that doing so may protect your safety or the safety of World Champion Network or others, or as otherwise permitted or required by law.

**  
7\. Children:**  World Champion Network does not intentionally collect information from children under 13 years of age. If you are under 13, you may not submit any information to World Champion Network.

**  
8\. Protection of Personal Information:**  World Champion Network uses reasonable administrative, physical and electronic security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of personal information.

No transmission of data over the internet is guaranteed to be completely secure. It may be possible for third parties not under the control of World Champion Network to intercept or access transmissions or private communications unlawfully. While we strive to protect personal information, neither World Champion Network nor our service providers can ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us over the internet. Any such transmission is at your own risk.

**  
9\. Updating Your Information:**  You are responsible for keeping your information current. You may update your information by contacting us at privacy@LegendsDigital.com. We will use reasonable efforts to process any change you make; provided, however, that requests to delete information are subject to World Champion Network’s internal reporting, processing, and retention policies and all applicable legal obligations.

**  
10\. Notice of Privacy Rights of California Residents:**  If you are a California resident and have provided personal information to World Champion Network, you are entitled by law to request certain information regarding any disclosure that may have been made by World Champion Network to third parties of personal information for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, send an email to privacy@LegendsDigital.com, specifying that you seek your "California Customer Choice Privacy Notice." Please allow thirty (30) days for a response. World Champion Network is required to respond to only one request per customer each year, and is not required to respond to requests made by means other than through the above email address.

We will not share your personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes if you request that we do not do so. You may make such a request by sending us an email at privacy@LegendsDigital.com. When contacting us, please indicate your name, address, email address, and what personal information you do not want us to share with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. Please note that there is no charge for controlling the sharing of your personal information or for processing this request.

**  
11\. Links:**  You may have the opportunity to follow links on the Service to other sites that may be of interest to you. World Champion Network endeavors to only link to reputable organizations. Because other sites may not be hosted or controlled by World Champion Network, we are not responsible for the privacy practices of those sites or the content provided thereon. Therefore, the privacy policies with respect to other sites may differ from those applicable to the Service. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of each other site. This Privacy Policy only applies to information collected and maintained by World Champion Network.

**  
12\. Questions:**  If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at privacy@LegendsDigital.com.
